How dare you say that my behavior is unacceptable
你怎能说我的行为令人无法接受
So condescending unnecessarily critical
如此不必要的屈尊带有批评的意味
I have the tendency of getting very physical
我有动粗的意向
So watch your step cause if I do you'll need a miracle
所以小心 因为一旦我采取行动你将需要奇迹(来解救自己)
You drain me dry and make me wonder why I'm even here
你将我慢慢耗干 让我不明白为什么自己还在这里
This Double Vision I was seeing is finally clear
过去不曾看清的模糊景象最终也变得清晰
You want to stay but you know very well I want you gone
你想留下但你很清楚其实我想让你离开
Not fit to funkin' tread the ground I'm walking on
我不想再这样惊恐的走下去
When it gets cold outside and you got nobody to love
当天气变冷你无人可以来爱时
You'll understand what I mean when I say
你就会明白我所说的
There's no way we're gonna give up
我们无路可走只能放弃
And like a little girl cries in the face of
a monster that lives in her dreams
就像小女孩在梦中的怪兽面前哭泣
Is there anyone out there cause it's getting harder and harder to breathe
有人吗 我已无法呼吸
What you are doing is screwing things up inside my head
你做的事情让我感到紧张
You should know better you never listened to a word I said
你最好知道我所说的你一句都没有听进去
Clutching your pillow and writhing in a naked sweat
抓紧枕头因痛苦而扭动身体
Hoping somebody someday will do you like I did
希望有一天会有人像我这样对待你
When it gets cold outside and you got nobody to love
当天气变冷你无人可以来爱时
You'll understand what I mean when I say
你就会明白我所说的
There's no way we're gonna give up
我们无路可走只能放弃
And like a little girl cries in the face of
a monster that lives in her dreams
就像小女孩在梦中的怪兽面前哭泣
Is there anyone out there cause it's getting harder and harder to breathe
有人吗 我已无法呼吸
Is there anyone out there
有人吗
Kill does it burn
灼伤会死人吗
Is it painful to learn
了解它很痛苦吗
That it's me that has all the control
那就是可以掌控一切的我
Thrill does it sting
刺你会紧张吗
When you feel what I bring
当你感受到我所带来的
And you wish that you had me to hold
你会希望你有我来支撑
When it gets cold outside and you got nobody to love
当天气变冷你无人可以来爱时
You'll understand what I mean when I say
你就会明白我所说的
There's no way we're gonna give up
我们无路可走只能放弃
And like a little girl cries in the face of
a monster that lives in her dreams
就像小女孩在梦中的怪兽面前哭泣
Is there anyone out there cause it's getting harder and harder to breathe
有人吗 我已无法呼吸
我感觉很好，你们好吗？！
能这里表演心情十分激动 谢谢你们
里约大会场！